{"questions":
[{
"question":"The world most famous monument 'pyramid' is located in..?",
"choices":["Russia","Iran","Egypt","Greece"],
"correctAnswer":"Egypt"


},
{
    "question":"The god of the sea in greek mythology is known as..?",
    "choices":["Poseidon","Calypso","Aries","Aphrodite"],
    "correctAnswer":"Poseidon"
    



},
{

"question":"Twitter is owned by..?",
"choices":["Elon Musk","Bill Gates","Jeff Bezos","Lionel Messsi"],
"correctAnswer":"Elon Musk"


},
{
    "question":"Which of these countries won the 2022 fifa world cup..?",
    "choices":["Argentina","Columbia","South Africa","Ghana"],
    "correctAnswer":"Argentina"


},
{
    
    "question":"One of the following is a hollywood movie director..?",
    "choices":["James Cameron","Randy Orton","Jennifer Lopez","Tyson Fury"],
    "correctAnswer":"James Cameron"


},
{
    
    "question":"The River Nile is locatedin which of these continents..?",
    "choices":["Australia","South America","Europe","Africa"],
    "correctAnswer":"Africa"


},
{
    "question":"The founder of microsoft is..?",
    "choices":["Bill Gates","Jeff Bezos","Elon Musk","Jennifer Lopez"],
    "correctAnswer":"Bill Gates"
    


},
{
    "question":"Batman is produced by one follwing...",
    "choices":["Marvel","Dc Comics","screen Gems","21st century fox"],
    "correctAnswer":"Dc Comics"

},
{
    
    "question":"The god of the war in greek mythology is known as...?",
    "choices":["Poseidon","Calypso","Aries","Aphrodite"],
    "correctAnswer":"Aries"


},
{
    "question":"The Uefa champions league was lifted in 2012 by which club..?",
    "choices":["Real Madrid fc","Chelsea fc","Arsenal fc","Bayern Fc"],
    "correctAnswer":"Chelsea fc"


}




]}